(Bernadette:)There were a few moments today
when I felt like we were a little family.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Bernadette:)I never thought of myself as a mom,
but when we were out...
...I felt like someday we could do it.
(Howard:)Of course we can.
(Howard:)Especially if our baby's
as calm and quiet as little Cinnam...
Son of a bitch, she's gone!
- Well, where'd she go?
- I don't know. She didn't leave a note.
You were supposed to put her
back in the stroller.
- No, I wasn't. You were.
- No, I wasn't.
- Yes, you were.
- Yeah, well, you throw like a girl.
(Sheldon:)I'm getting worried.
(Penny:)Relax, Sheldon,
he's only a few minutes late.
(Sheldon:)Professor Proton was never late
when he was on TV.
You know, every day, 4:00, he was there.
(Sheldon:)Unless tornadoes were ripping apart
East Texas, then we'd join him in progress.